http://www.custombuildingproducts.com/privacy.aspx

CustomTech Flooring Prep
CustomTech – the industry’s leading collection of technologically-superior, easy-to-use, professional grade subfloor preparation products designed for all types of floor coverings.
View All CustomTech Flooring Prep Products
Surface Prep
Self-Leveling Underlayments
Mud Bed and Patching Compounds
Waterproofing Membranes & Underlayments
Pre-Mixed
Cement Backerboards
Surface Primers
Wall Patching
Surface Prep
Quality begins from the ground up.
Preparing your surface is the most critical task of any tile or stone installation. Custom Building Products offers you one source for the needs of virtually any job.
Download the
Custom Building Products Catalog
View All Surface Prep Products
Setting
Polymer-Modified Thin-Set Mortars
Large Format Tile Mortars
Thick Bed Mortar
Rapid Setting Mortars
Setting
The foundation of precise tile and stone setting.
Whatever the application, CUSTOM®
offers the broadest line of tile and stone setting materials in the industry to give the exact performance your job demands.
Download theCustom Building Products Catalog
View All Setting Products
Grout
Single Component® Grout
Epoxy Grout
Cement Grout
Pre-Mixed Grout
Caulk & Sealant
Grout Additives
Grout Colorant
Slider - Prism Color
Slider - Stain Resistant
Grout
Tile grout with dependable performance and color.
Look for tile grout with rock-solid durability, consistency and the largest color palette with Custom. Our grouts are easy to work with yet deliver hard, dense joints.
Download the
Custom Building Products Catalog
View All Grout Products
Care & Maintenance
Sealers
Enhancers
Cleaners
Problem Solvers
Stone Restoration
Grout Colorant
Grout Additives
Travertine Repair Kit
Care & Maintenance
Stains can RUIN Stone & Tile.Protect Yours Now!
Stains on stone, tile or grout happen easily - and can leave permanent stains. Protect your surface against both oil-based and water-based stains with the right sealer.
Download the
Custom Building Products Catalog
View All Care & Maintenance Products
Aqua Mix®
Sealers
Enhancers
Cleaners
Problem Solvers
Stone Restoration
Grout Colorant
Aqua Mix®
Professional Solutions for Professional Results
Offering the largest selection of Sealers, Cleaners, Problem Solvers, Grout Colorant and Stone Restoration products, we provide professionals with the right tools and solutions; making us the #1 Contractor Preferred Manufacturer of Sealers and Cleaners.
Download theAqua Mix® Catalog
View All Aqua Mix® Products
Tools & Accessories
Cut & Mark Tools
Prep Tools
Setting Tools
Grout & Finish Tools
Tools & Accessories
Precision demands the best.
SuperiorBilt® Tools are professionally preferred for tile, stone and floor covering installations.
Download the
Tools & Accessories Catalog
View All Tools & Accessories Products
All Products A-Z
Reference Library
Safety Data Sheets
Technical Data Sheets
Case Studies
Privacy Policy
Custom Building Products recognizes that you care how information about you is used and shared. We created this Privacy Policy to inform you of our information collection, use and sharing practices for this Web site.
Please be advised that the practices described in this Privacy Policy apply only to information gathered through this Web site and, where applicable, through our Customer Service or Technical Support Departments in connection with this web site and do not necessarily reflect our practices with respect to information gathered through other means.
If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, contact our Marketing Department by email at news@cbpmail.net.
Information Collection and Storage We collect and store certain information automatically. For example, we collect your IP address, browser information and reference site domain name every time you visit this Web site. We also collect information regarding user traffic patterns and site usage. This information is used to analyze and improve this Web site and to provide our customers with a fulfilling experience.
Also, like many web sites, we use "cookies", which are files stored on your computer's hard drive by your browser to help us identify user types. Most browsers accept cookies automatically but allow you to disable them. We recommend that you leave cookies turned on so we can offer you a better experience on this Web site.
Sharing Information We do not share with others any personal information that you provide to us through this Web site or through our Customer Service or Technical Support Departments, except with your consent or as described in this Privacy Policy.
Custom Building Products engages third parties to perform services in connection with the operation of our business. Examples of these services include marketing and promotional material distribution, web site evaluation and data analysis.
We may share non-personal information with our marketing partners, advertisers and others from time to time. Examples of such non-personal information include the number of users who visited this Web site during a specific time period. This information generally is shared in an aggregated form.
Linking To or From Another Web Site This web site may contain links to Web sites operated by third parties. Please be advised that the practices described in this Privacy Policy do not apply to information gathered through these other Web sites. We encourage you to be aware of when you leave this Web site and to read the privacy policies of each and every Web site that you visit. Custom Building Products is not responsible for the content, security or privacy policies used by other company's web sites.
If you have accessed this Web site through a link from our advertising or marketing partners, this Web site may include a frame of the applicable advertising or marketing partner. Nevertheless, the information you provide to us through these framed Web pages is collected by us and our use of this information is governed by this Privacy Policy.
Changes to our Privacy Policy If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will post a notice on this Web site notifying users of the changes. Please check this Web site periodically to see if any recent changes to this Privacy Policy have occurred.
MOBILE PRIVACY POLICY
Custom Building Products recognizes that you care how information about you is used and shared. We created this Mobile Privacy Policy to inform you of our information collection, use and sharing practices for this mobile application.
Please be advised that the practices described in this Mobile Privacy Policy apply only to information gathered through this Application and, where applicable, through our Customer Service or Technical Support Departments in connection with this Application and do not necessarily reflect our practices with respect to information gathered through other means.
If you have any questions regarding this Mobile Privacy Policy, contact our Marketing Department by email at news@cbpmail.net.
User Provided Information
The Application does not require registration to be downloaded or used. If you utilize the Contact Us portion of the Application, you will be required to provide the following information: (a) First Name; (b) Last Name; (c) Email Address; (d) Nature of Inquiry; (e) Comments.
We may use the information you provide us to contact you with important information, required notices and marketing promotions.
Automatically Collected Information
In addition, the Application may collect certain information automatically, including, but not limited to, the type of mobile device you use, your mobile device’s unique device ID, the IP address of your mobile device, your mobile operating system, the type of mobile Internet browsers you use, and information about the way you use the Application.
Third Party Information
Only aggregated, anonymized data is periodically transmitted to external services to help us improve the Application and our service. We will share your information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy statement.
We may disclose User Provided and Automatically Collected Information:
as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process;
when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request;
with our trusted services providers who work on our behalf, do not have an independent use of the information we disclose to them, and have agreed to adhere to the rules set forth in this privacy statement.
if Custom Building Products is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of this information, as well as any choices you may have regarding this information.
Opt-out Rights
You can stop all collection of information by the Application easily by uninstalling the Application. You may use the standard uninstall processes as may be available as part of your mobile device or via the mobile application marketplace or network. You can also request to opt-out via email, at news@cbpmail.net
Data Retention Policy, Managing Your Information
We will retain User Provided data for as long as you use the Application and for a reasonable time thereafter. We will retain Automatically Collected information for up to 24 months and thereafter may store it in aggregate. If you’d like us to delete User Provided Data that you have provided via the Application, please contact us at news@cbpmail.net and we will respond in a reasonable time. Please note that some or all of the User Provided Data may be required in order for the Application to function properly.
Children
We do not use the Application to knowingly solicit data from or market to children under the age of 13. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with information without their consent, he or she should contact us at news@cbpmail.net. We will delete such information from our files within a reasonable time.
Security
We are concerned about safeguarding the confidentiality of your information. We provide physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect information we process and maintain. For example, we limit access to this information to authorized employees and contractors who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our Application. Please be aware that, although we endeavor to provide reasonable security for information we process and maintain, no security system can prevent all potential security breaches.
Changes to our Mobile Privacy Policy
If we make any material changes to this Mobile Privacy Policy, we will post a notice on this Application notifying users of the changes. Please check this Application periodically to see if any recent changes to this Mobile Privacy Policy have occurred.
Terms of Use
By using the Application, you are consenting to our processing of your information as set forth in this Mobile Privacy Policy now and as amended by us. "Processing,” means using cookies on a computer/hand held device or using or touching information in any way, including, but not limited to, collecting, storing, deleting, using, combining and disclosing information, all of which activities will take place in the United States. If you reside outside the United States your information will be transferred, processed and stored there under United States privacy standards.
Limitation of Liabilities
Under no circumstances will Custom® Building Products be liable to any person or business entity for any direct, indirect, special, incidental, consequential or other damages based on any use of this mobile application including, without limitation, any lost profits, business interruption or loss of programs or information, even if Custom® Building Products has been specifically advised of the possibility of such damages.
Contact Us
If you have any questions regarding privacy while using the Application, or have questions about our practices, please contact us via email at news@cbpmail.net.
Privacy Policy
CUSTOM BUILDING PRODUCTS
Customer Support800-272-8786
Technical Services800-282-8786
Mailing Address Custom Building Products 7711 Center Ave. Ste 500 Huntington Beach, CA 92647
© 2020 Custom Building Products. All Rights Reserved. Privacy
